Finding Aid for William G. Milliken papers 1961-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Administrative / Executive Files
  - Internal Memoranda and Correspondence, 32 linear feet
    - Staff
      - 1982
        - Law, Bob (Box 621)
        - Lee, Albert (Box 621)
        - Long, Bill (Box 621)
        - Lukens, Bill (Box 621)
        - McCarthy, Pat (Box 621)
        - McLogan, Matthew (Box 621)
        - Miller, Gerald, 2 folders (Box 621)
        - Monroe, Loren (Box 621)
        - Neuroth, Joann (Box 621)
        - Oettle, Ken (Box 621)
        - Payne, Dennis (Box 621)
        - Pelloso, Thomas (Box 621)
        - Pinkelman, Franklin (Box 621)
        - Pratt, Stan (Box 621)
        - Pridgeon, Dean (Box 621)
        - Quincy, Ron (Box 621)
        - Rasmussen, Beth (Box 621)
        - Ruff, Craig (Box 621)
        - Roberts, Doug (Box 621)
        - Runkel, Phillip (Box 622)
        - Rustem, Bill (Box 622)
        - Sandner, Al (Box 622)
        - Saxton, Isabel (Box 622)
        - Schlaff, Richard (Box 622)
        - Schneidewind, Eric (Box 622)
        - Seger, Martha (Box 622)
        - Skuggen, Bob (Box 622)
        - Slotsema, Linda (Box 622)
        - Smith, Doug (Box 622)
        - Tanner, Howard (Box 622)
        - Tatzmann, Manfred (Box 622)
        - Taylor, Martin (Box 622)
        - Van Tien, Fred (Box 622)
        - Walker, Bailus (Box 622)
        - Walters, Peter (Box 622)
        - Weeks, George (Box 622)
        - Weems, Beth (Box 622)
        - Wiledon, Peter (Box 622)
        - Woodford, John (Box 622)
      - Miscellaneous 1969-1982 (Box 622)
    - Subject Files 1969-1982
      - Administrative Board 1980 (Box 623)
      - Art in State Buildings 1976, 1980, 2 folders (Box 623)
      - Budget 1972, 1982, 2 folders (Box 623)
      - Campus Unrest (Box 623)
      - Chrysler (Box 623)
      - City/State Relations (Box 623)
      - Civil Rights Commission 1972 (Box 623)
      - Clay, Cassius 1970, 2 folders (Box 623)
      - Commerce 1975-1977 (Box 623)
      - Comprehensive Health Planning 1971 (Box 623)
      - Corrections 1975-1977 (Box 623)
      - Department Heads 1980-1982, 3 folders (Box 623)
      - Development, Community, 2 folders (Box 623)
      - Double Bottom Tankers (Box 623)
      - Energy 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 623)
      - Executive Clemency Actions 1980 (Box 624)
      - Executive Office 1969-1975, 2 folders (Box 624)
      - Executive Orders 1970-1982, 7 folders (Box 624)
      - Governor's Conference 1977 (Box 624)
      - Governor's Small Business Council 1977 (Box 624)
      - Grants 1980-1982, 3 folders (Box 624)
      - Hiring Freeze 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 624)
      - Indian Fishing (Box 624)
      - Institutionalization (Box 624)
      - Issues (Box 624)
      - Judicial Elections 1979 (Box 624)
      - Laetrile 1975-1979 (Box 624)
      - Legal Drinking Age (Box 624)
      - Legislation 1971-1980, 5 folders (Box 624)
      - Licensing and Regulation, 2 folders (Box 625)
      - Lincoln Day 1971-1973 (Box 625)
      - Liquor Commission 1968-1971 (Box 625)
      - Mackinac Bridge Authority Investigation (Box 625)
      - Management Sciences Group (Box 625)
      - Mental Health Institutions, Visits 1976-1978 (Box 625)
      - Michigan Manpower Commission (Box 625)
      - Migrants (Box 625)
      - Military Affairs 1969-1971 (Box 625)
      - National Advisory Council on Adult Education (Box 625)
      - National Convention 1979 (Box 625)
      - Nuclear Waste 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 625)
      - Operation Breakthrough, HUD 1969-1971 (Box 625)
      - PBB 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 625)
      - Pigeon River (Box 625)
      - Pope Shenouda III of Alexandria 1977 (Box 625)
      - Program Budget Evaluation System (Box 625)
      - Proposal A 1981 (Box 625)
      - Proposal C 1972 (Box 626)
      - Racing Commission Investigation 1970 (Box 626)
      - Recreation Bonds 1969 (Box 626)
      - Republican Political Reform 1976 (Box 626)
      - Republican State Central Committee 1969-1971 (Box 626)
      - Republican State Nationalities 1969-1971 (Box 626)
      - Residence of the Governor 1969-1970 (Box 626)
      - Revenue Sharing 1979 (Box 626)
      - Riverside Industrial Park 1977 (Box 626)
      - Roth Decision (Bussing) 1972 (Box 626)
      - Rural Affairs, Governor's Council on (Box 626)
      - Seafarer (Project) 1977 (Box 626)
      - Single Business Tax 1977 (Box 626)
      - Solomon, Sam (Box 626)
      - Stadium (Detroit) 1971 (Box 626)
      - Staff Meeting 1972 (Box 626)
      - State Fair Commission Report 1977 (Box 626)
      - Tax Tribunal 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 626)
      - Thank-You Letters 1977-1980, 3 folders (Box 626)
      - Total Research in Improved Management (Box 626)
      - Transportation (Box 626)
      - Travel, Out-of-State 1979 (Box 626)
      - Travel Regulations (Box 626)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 2 folders (Box 626)
      - Upper Peninsula Office 1981 (Box 626)
      - Urban/Urban Affairs, 2 folders (Box 626)
      - Welfare Reform 1970-1971 (Box 626)
      - Worker's Compensation Reform 1975 (Box 626)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 626)
  - Staff Files, 224 linear feet
    The Staff Files series consists of policy and operational papers created by many executive office staff. Materials include memoranda, correspondence, reports, agenda and minutes, legal briefs and decisions, press releases, clippings, and printed works. Files also contain items referred to as briefing, or issues, books. These chronological notebooks serve as the governor's briefing tool for establishing executive policy by compiling reports, correspondence, and memos that analyze priorities, provide background information, and recommend legislative/executive action.
    Files are arranged by staff person rather than by office or subject and, therefore, do not readily accommodate research of a single topic. A subject approach to the series is further impeded by its size, 224 linear feet. Yet this series contains the bulk of the collection's topical materials. For example, Staff Files include rich source materials on economic growth and development, education, transportation, human services, women's rights, labor, minorities, urban affairs, PBB and toxic wastes, nuclear energy, and similar matters. Several techniques may prove helpful when doing research: Use Appendix A (Index to Staff Files) and Appendix B (Staff Listing); these general lists may provide some direction for searching. Search the Ellsworth/Frankland sequence first (see Research Strategy for Use). Refer to the subject files of Internal Memoranda and Correspondence. If your topic appears, note the staff member responsible, then search their files.
    Several filing traits are distinctive to this series. Topical files, as commonly understood, include many formats of material, but are not characterized by singular runs of correspondence or memoranda. Within the Staff Files, subseries of correspondence or memoranda often have been placed within topical sequences, filed under 'C' or 'M' respectively. The staff materials, as a whole, were created between 1965 and 1982. Each subseries of staff member's papers have been individually dated within this time frame, but these dates are only approximate.
    Of special note are the files of Isabella Saxton, head of Milliken's Communications Unit. These files include studies and recommendations on the reorganization of work in the offices responsible for citizen mail, summary mail counts, content analysis of letters received, and memoranda. Saxton's files also include ROBO responses to constituent correspondence; these machine-generated outgoing letters delineate the administration's positions on issues of the day.
    The Early Program Material files, 1968-1973, are of import in that they document the early years of Milliken's tenure, before administrative reorganization. They include materials on human services and educational issues, records of the Executive Office, Programs and Policies, budgets, files on health, crime, economic opportunity, law enforcement and criminal justice, planning and youth, and state financing of local education.
    - Office of Lieutenant Governor 1979-1982
      - Topical Files
        - Annexation (Box 627)
        - Block Grant (Box 627)
        - Bruce Crossing, State Police in (Box 627)
        - Carmel Hall (Box 627)
        - Commerce (Box 627)
        - Criminal Justice (Box 627)
        - Development Choices for the 80s (Box 627)
        - Economic Development (Box 627)
        - Education (Box 627)
        - ELF Project (Box 627)
        - Energy (Box 627)
        - Enterprise Zones (Box 627)
        - Environment (Box 627)
        - Environmental Protection (Box 627)
        - Flint Monorail (Box 627)
        - Higher Education Capital Investment (Box 627)
        - Holley, Reverend Jim (Box 627)
        - Ingham County (Box 627)
        - Juvenile Code Revision (Box 627)
        - Koinola Medical Foundation (Box 627)
        - Lansing (Box 627)
        - Lindell Drop Forge (Box 627)
        - Marijuana Bill (Box 627)
        - Maybank Amendment (Defense Purchases) (Box 627)
        - Michigan State Housing Authority (Box 627)
        - National Conference of Lt. Governors (Box 627)
        - Natural Resources (Mineral Leasing) (Box 627)
        - Navigable Waters (Box 627)
        - Oil and Gas Industry (Box 627)
        - Pension Fund (Box 627)
        - Pontiac Stadium Subsidy (Box 627)
        - Public Employees Right to Strike (Box 627)
        - Regulatory Review (Box 627)
        - Reuse of Vacant Public Buildings (Box 627)
        - SEMCOG (Southeast Michigan Council of Gov'ts.) (Box 627)
        - Small Business (Box 627)
        - Solid Waste Disposal in U.P (Box 627)
        - State Shared Funds (Fire Protection) (Box 627)
        - Telegraph Lines and Companies (HB 5560) (Box 627)
        - Traverse City (Box 627)
        - Traverse City Hilton (Box 627)
        - Treasury, Department of (Box 627)
        - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 627)
      - Community Development Cabinet
        - General Communications 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 628)
        - Agricultural Preservation Strategy (Box 628)
        - Alternative Growth Patterns in Michigan (Box 628)
        - Battle Creek (Box 628)
        - Bay County (Box 628)
        - Benton Harbor (Box 628)
        - Brighton NPDES Permit (Box 628)
        - Community Development Office, 2 folders (Box 628)
        - Enterprise Zones (Box 628)
        - Environmental Protection (Box 628)
        - Facility Sites Selection (Box 628)
        - Hamtramck/Chrysler (Box 628)
        - Land Value Tax System (Box 628)
        - Local Audits (Financial Emergencies) (Box 628)
        - M-275 (Highway) (Box 628)
        - Pontiac General Motors Plant (Box 628)
        - Regional Planning Committee Act (Box 628)
        - Rural Development Council (Box 628)
        - SB 817 (and HB 4371) (Box 628)
        - Small and Rural Communities Task Force (Box 628)
        - State Reorganization (Box 628)
        - SWEDDA (Southwest Detroit Development Assoc.) (Box 628)
        - Targeted Jobs Tax Credit (Box 628)
        - Traverse City Psychiatric Hospital (Box 628)
        - Water Quality Management Plan (Box 628)
    - Gordon Alexander 1968-1982
      - Topical Files
        - Affirmative Action 1975-1980
          - Affirmative Action Task Force Minutes 1975 (Box 629)
          - Civil Service 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 629)
          - Executive Office 1977-1979, 3 folders (Box 629)
          - General Materials 1975-1980, 7 folders (Box 629)
        - Audits 1968-1979, 3 folders (Box 629)
        - Budget 1973-1981
          - 1973-1974 (Box 629)
          - 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box 629)
          - 1975-1976, 4 folders (Box 630)
          - 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 630)
          - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 630)
          - 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 630)
          - 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 630)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 630)
          - Notebooks 1974-1981, 7 folders (Box 631)
          - Report on Deficit at Kalamazoo Regional Psychiatric Hospital 1978 (Box 631)
          - Requests and Briefings 1974-1975
            - Department of Education (Box 631)
            - Insurance Bureau (Box 631)
            - Wayne State University (Box 631)
        - Departments and Commissions
          - General 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box 631)
          - Art in State Buildings 1976-1977 (Box 631)
          - Juvenile Justice 1975-1976 (Box 631)
          - Michigan Equal Opportunity Commission 1976-1980, 5 folders (Box 631)
          - Volunteer in Michigan 1974-1976, 2 folders (Box 631)
          - Fleet Safety Program 1975-1976 (Box 632)
          - Michigan Legacy 1976 (Box 632)
          - National Science Foundation 1975-1978, 4 folders (Box 632)
          - Washington Office 1979-1980 (Box 632)
      - Administrative Memoranda and Correspondence
        - Personnel 1980 (Box 632)
        - Political Reimbursements 1980 (Box 632)
        - Staff 1977-1981, 3 folders (Box 632)
        - Temporary Clerical Help 1980 (Box 632)
        - Training Programs (Civil Service) 1979 (Box 632)
        - Miscellaneous 1978-1979 (Box 632)
    - Glenn Allen 1965-1973
      - Administrative Services 1972 (Box 632)
      - Airplane Purchase (Mitsubishi MU2-F) (Box 632)
      - Budget 1968-1972
        - 1968-1969 (Box 632)
        - 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 632)
        - 1970-1971, 4 folders (Box 632)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 632)
      - Chamber of Commerce (Box 632)
      - Citizens' Research Council (Box 632)
      - Constitutional Amendments (Box 632)
      - Council of State Governments (Box 632)
      - Detroit
        - Stadium, 3 folders (Box 633)
        - Stadium and Fair Development, 2 folders (Box 633)
        - Wayne County (Box 633)
      - Economic Club Debate (Box 633)
      - Economic Outlook (Trends) (Box 633)
      - Economic Review and Outlook (Michigan) (Box 633)
      - Education Reform
        - Message 1971 (Box 633)
        - Taxes/Projections, 3 folders (Box 633)
      - Executive Office 1972 (Box 633)
      - Executive Orders 1966-1972 (Box 633)
      - Gas Tax Increase 1971 (Box 633)
      - General Departmental Communications 1969-1973, 17 folders (Box 633)
      - Governor Milliken Memoranda 1972 (Box 633)
      - Governor's Commissions (Box 633)
      - Hospital Finance Authority (Box 633)
      - Housing Bonding II (Box 633)
      - Labor Department Investigation (Box 633)
      - Legislative 1970-1972, 11 folders (Box 634)
      - Local Government, Governor's Commission on (Box 634)
      - Message Appendix (Box 634)
      - Michigan Education Association (Box 634)
      - Nursing Homes (Box 634)
      - Off-Track Betting 1972 (Box 634)
      - Other States 1968 (Box 634)
      - Outstate 1968-1973 (Box 634)
      - Pornography 1973 (Box 635)
      - Property Tax 1971-1972 (Box 635)
      - Public Health Legislation 1970 (Box 635)
      - Reorganization 1966-1973, 2 folders (Box 635)
      - Republican Party 1967-1971 (Box 635)
      - Retirement Funds 1965-1972, 2 folders (Box 635)
      - School Aid 1966-1973 (Box 635)
      - Small Loans (HB 4195) 1971 (Box 635)
      - State-Local Revenue Sharing 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 635)
      - State Lottery 1971-1972 (Box 635)
      - State of the State 1972 (Box 635)
      - Transportation Package, 3 folders (Box 635)
      - Unclassified Salaries (Box 635)
      - United States (Miscellaneous) (Box 635)
      - Vietnam Veterans Bonus 1972 (Box 635)
      - Wage-Price Freeze 1971 (Box 635)
      - Welfare 1970 (Box 635)
      - Willow Run Laboratory/Project 1972-1973 (Box 635)
      - Zollar (Senator) 1968-1970 (Box 635)
    - Holly Angell, 1978-82
      - Michigan Council for the Arts
        - Advisory Panel Reports (Box 636)
        - Arts Outreach Program, FY 1980 (Box 636)
        - Budget 1980-83, 3 folders (Box 636)
        - Budget Hearing, Departmental August 24, 1979 (Box 636)
        - Budget Request, FY 1980 (Box 636)
        - Budget Request and Hearings, FY 1982 (Box 636)
        - Council Meetings November 7, 1979-August 25, 1982, 14 folders (Box 636)
        - Grants and Funding (Programs and Guidelines), 1979-83 (Box 636)
        - Graphic Standards Manual (Box 636)
        - Guidelines and Forms, FY 1982 (Box 636)
        - Handbook, FY 1980 (Box 636)
        - Legislative Hearing
          - House Appropriations Subcommittee
            - February 26, 1980 (Box 636)
            - March 16, 1982 (Box 636)
          - Senate Appropriations Subcommittee 1980 (Box 636)
        - Legislative Report
          - FY 1978 (Box 636)
          - FY 1981 (Box 636)
        - Newsletters (Box 636)
        - Operational Support Program to Discipline Oriented Arts Organizations, FY 1980 (Box 636)
        - Program Guidelines
          - Office of General Services 1980 (Box 636)
          - Office of Artist Services 1981 (Box 636)
          - Office of Developmental Services, 2 folders (Box 636)
          - Office of Expansion Services 1981 (Box 636)
        - Resource Directory, 1981-82 (Box 636)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 636)
      - Michigan History Division
        - 1981 Historic Preservation Fund Work Program (Box 636)
        - Grant and Funding Information (Box 636)
      - Topical Files
        - Abortion (Box 637)
        - Art and Education (Box 637)
        - Art in Public Buildings, Commission on (Box 637)
        - Art in Public Places Bill (Box 637)
        - Art, Native American (Box 637)
        - Artrain (Box 637)
        - Arts
          - Awards (Box 637)
          - Budget, 2 folders (Box 637)
          - Handicapped (Box 637)
        - Baldwin High School (Box 637)
        - Boarshead (Box 637)
        - Campaign 1980 (Box 637)
        - Civil Rights Report (Box 637)
        - Clinton Valley Center (SB 489) (Box 637)
        - Coldwater Mental Health Center, 2 folders (Box 637)
        - Commission on Art in State Buildings (Box 637)
        - Heizer Speech Dedication/Groundbreaking (Box 637)
        - Community Art Agencies (Local groups) (Box 637)
        - Congress on the Arts (Box 637)
        - Creative Arts Alliance (Box 637)
        - Cuba (Bill Nelson) (Box 637)
        - Detroit Council for the Arts (Box 637)
        - Detroit Institute of Arts
          - General 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 637)
          - Show on the Road (Box 637)
        - Detroit Symphony Orchestra (Box 637)
        - Diamond Reo (Box 637)
        - Dominican Republic Art Show (Box 637)
        - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 637)
        - Ethnicity and Folk Arts in Detroit (Box 638)
        - Gerald R. Ford Museum/Library (Box 638)
        - Foreign Affairs (Box 638)
        - Fredricks, Marshall (Box 638)
        - Friend of the Court, 2 folders (Box 638)
        - Glass Month (Box 638)
        - Grand Rapids
          - Art Museum (Box 638)
          - Symphony (Box 638)
        - Grosse Ile Customs House (Box 638)
        - Historic Preservation (Box 638)
        - Historic Tax Act (Box 638)
        - Historical Society of Michigan (Box 638)
        - History Book (Lansing) (Box 638)
        - Impression 5 Museum (Lansing), 2 folders (Box 638)
        - Interlochen (Box 638)
        - Iran Hostages Absentee Vote (Peter McCann) (Box 638)
        - Keep Michigan Beautiful (Box 638)
        - Mental Health Traveling Museum (Box 638)
        - Michigan Council for the Humanities (Box 638)
        - Michigan History Division (Box 638)
        - Michigan International Council (Box 638)
        - Michigan Partners of the Americas (Box 638)
        - Milliken Foundation (Box 638)
        - Mural Art (Box 638)
        - Opera (Michigan Opera Theatre) (Box 638)
        - Orchestra Hall (Box 639)
        - Osborn, Chase (Box 639)
        - Pewabic Art (Box 639)
        - Preservation Conference (Box 639)
        - Queen Beatrix's Visit (Box 639)
        - Sesquicentennial (Box 639)
        - State
          - Buildings (Surplus) (Box 639)
          - Song Proposal (Box 639)
          - Library (Box 639)
        - State of the State 1979-1982, 4 folders (Box 639)
        - Statue of George Washington (Box 639)
        - Summerthing Art Festival 1980 (Box 639)
        - Traverse City Regional Hospital, 2 folders (Box 639)
        - Traverse City Opera House (Box 639)
        - United Nations Association of U.S.A (Box 639)
        - United Nations Day 1980-1982 (Box 639)
        - Veteran's Memorial (Box 639)
        - Women's Assembly III (Box 639)
        - Women's Commission
          - General 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 639)
          - Comparable Worth Study (Box 639)
        - Women and Pregnancy (Box 639)
        - Women's Hall of Fame (Box 639)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Former Staffers (Atchley, 2 folders) (Box 639)
          - Correspondence 1979-1982 (Box 639)
    - Patrick Babcock 1969-1978
      - Cabinet Notebooks
        - Consumer Protection and Regulatory 1977 (Box 640)
        - Economic Growth and Development 1976-1978 (Box 640)
        - Environment and Land Use 1976-1978 (Box 640)
        - Justice 1975-1977 (Box 640)
        - Labor and Economic Development 1976 (Box 640)
        - Regulatory 1975-1976 (Box 640)
      - Topical Files
        - Aging
          - General 1977 (Box 640)
          - Director Search 1977 (Box 640)
          - House Bill 4139, 1976 (Box 640)
        - Agriculture 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 640)
        - Appointments 1977 (Box 640)
        - Builders' Association 1977 (Box 640)
        - Cable TV 1977 (Box 640)
        - Civil Rights 1974 (Box 640)
        - Civil Service 1974-1977, 3 folders (Box 640)
        - Commerce
          - General 1975-1977, 3 folders (Box 641)
          - Legislation 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 641)
        - Community Affairs 1975-1976 (Box 641)
        - Corrections 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 641)
        - Cultural Complex (State) 1976-1977 (Box 641)
        - Damman, James T. (Lt. Gov.) 1974-1977 (Box 641)
        - Data Processing (ADP) 1977 (Box 641)
        - Daylight Savings Time (Box 641)
        - Democratic Tape Lines (House/Senate) 1975 (Box 641)
        - Detroit 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 641)
        - Drinking Age 1977 (Box 641)
        - Economic Growth and Development
          - General 1977 (Box 642)
          - Cabinet/Council, 2 folders (Box 642)
        - Education 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 642)
        - Energy
          - General 1976-1977, 5 folders (Box 642)
          - Administration Briefing Book 1978 (Box 642)
        - Federal Issues 1977 (Box 642)
        - Foreign Affairs 1977 (Box 642)
        - Highways 1974-1978, 2 folders (Box 642)
        - Human Services 1975, 2 folders (Box 642)
        - Kinchloe Air Base 1976-1977 (Box 643)
        - Labor
          - General 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 643)
          - Audits (Box 643)
          - Bureau of Safety and Regulation 1975 (Box 643)
          - MESC 1973-1975 (Box 643)
          - Project 95 1976 (Box 643)
        - Law Enforcement 1976 (Box 643)
        - Legislative Priorities 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 643)
        - Licensing/Regulation 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 643)
        - Lottery 1974-1975 (Box 643)
        - Management and Budget 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 643)
        - Martin Place Inc. 1977 (Box 643)
        - Mental Health 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 643)
        - Merrill-Palmer Institute 1977 (Box 643)
        - Michigan Economic Action Council 1974-1977 (Box 643)
        - Michigan Efficiency Task Force
          - General 1976-1977, 3 folders (Box 643)
          - General 1977-1978, 5 folders (Box 644)
        - Michigan State Housing Development Authority
          - General 1976-1977, 3 folders (Box 644)
          - Audits/Background 1969-1977, 2 folders (Box 644)
        - Minority and Small Businesses 1975-1977 (Box 644)
        - Motor Carrier Enforcement 1977 (Box 644)
        - National Health Insurance 1975-1977 (Box 645)